

DATE OF BIRTH: 27/06/1984

CONTACT

Nationality: Slovenian

Gender: Male

Trnovski pristan 8, 1000 Ljubljana, Slovenia



(+386) 04510487



ABOUT ME

Played online poker player for 12 year and now looking to dip my toes into programming. Started with Python programming language and completed couple of courses on https://dataquest.io/. Courses focused mainly on data processing and data visualization from CSV files and SQL databases. After searching for some job prospects I decided to go WebDev route. With the help of https://www.theodinproject.com/ and its community I learned CSS, HTML and Javascript for frontend and Node.js, Express.js and MongoDB database for backend. I continue to learn on my own and im currently focusing on Vue.js and Nuxt.js technologies.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

1999 - 2003

Secondary School of Economics: economic technician Šolski center Postoina

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/2006 - 08/2006 - Podskrajnik, Slovenia

Factory worker

Ydria Motors d.o.o.

I worked on and help maintain different factory machines and working behind the assembly line.

2007 - 2018

Online poker player

self-employed

During the summer of 2006 friend introduced me to poker training site and by the end of 2007 I went "professional". Besides playing poker itself I spent a lot of time studying the game - alone and with players around the world, used different programs for overall analysis of the game (Hold'em Manager, Poker Tracker), analysis of specific situations (Power Equilab, ICM ...) and game theory optimal simulators (PIO solver, SimplePostflop). In the past online poker rooms were quite crude thats why I created a couple of autohotkey (AHK) scripts, for better UX, and table mods for more transparent table view.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Slovenian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
C1	C2	production	interaction	B2
		B2	B2	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Web Development: HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript / NodeJS and ExpressJs / GIT (GitHub) / JSON / Vue.js, Vuex, NuxtJS / Firebase (Functions, Auth, Firestore, Storage) / Currently learning MongoDB.